Ann Cottrell Free Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Notebooks and Diaries, 1933-2004 (Box 237-289)
  Material types include notebooks, diaries, journals, daybooks, and note cards.
  Arranged chronologically.
  - 1933-1935 (Box 237)
  - 1936-circa 1936, (3 folders) (Box 238)
  - circa 1936-1939, (4 folders) (Box 239)
  - 1930s, (3 folders) (Box 240)
  - 1940-1943 (Box 240)
  - 1944-1947, (6 folders) (Box 241)
  - 1947-1949, (3 folders) (Box 242)
  - 1940s (Box 243)
  - 1950-1953, (2 folders) (Box 243)
  - 1954-1956, (3 folders) (Box 244)
  - 1957-1958, (3 folders) (Box 245)
  - 1959, (2 folders) (Box 246)
  - 1950s (Box 246)
  - 1950s (Box 247)
  - 1960, (2 folders) (Box 247)
  - 1960-1961, (3 folders) (Box 248)
  - 1962-1963, (3 folders) (Box 249)
  - 1963-1964, (3 folders) (Box 250)
  - 1964-1967, undated, (3 folders) (Box 251)
  - 1965-1966, (3 folders) (Box 252)
  - 1967-1968, (3 folders) (Box 253)
  - 1968-1969, (4 folders) (Box 254)
  - 1969 (Box 255)
  - 1960s, (2 folders) (Box 255)
  - 1970-1971, (3 folders) (Box 256)
  - 1971-1972, (3 folders) (Box 257)
  - 1972-1973, (3 folders) (Box 258)
  - 1973-1974, (3 folders) (Box 259)
  - 1974-1975, (4 folders) (Box 260)
  - 1975-1976, (3 folders) (Box 261)
  - 1976-1977, (4 folders) (Box 262)
  - 1977-1978, (3 folders) (Box 263)
  - 1978-1979, (2 folders) (Box 264)
  - 1970s (Box 264)
  - 1970s, (3 folders) (Box 265)
  - 1970s, (4 folders) (Box 266)
  - 1980-1982, (4 folders) (Box 267)
  - 1982-1984, (3 folders) (Box 268)
  - 1984-1986, (4 folders) (Box 269)
  - 1986-1988, (4 folders) (Box 270)
  - 1987-1988, (3 folders) (Box 271)
  - 1988-1989, (5 folders) (Box 272)
  - 1989, (2 folders) (Box 273)
  - 1980s (Box 273)
  - 1980s, (3 folders) (Box 274)
  - 1980s, (3 folders) (Box 275)
  - 1990, (3 folders) (Box 275)
  - 1990-1992, (3 folders) (Box 276)
  - 1991, (3 folders) (Box 277)
  - 1992-1993, (3 folders) (Box 278)
  - 1993-1994, (3 folders) (Box 279)
  - 1994-1995, (3 folders) (Box 280)
  - 1995-1996, (3 folders) (Box 281)
  - 1996-1997, (4 folders) (Box 282)
  - 1998-1999, (3 folders) (Box 283)
  - 1990s, (3 folders) (Box 284)
  - 2000 (Box 284)
  - 2001-2002, (4 folders) (Box 285)
  - 2003-2004, (2 folders) (Box 286)
  - Undated, (2 folders) (Box 286)
  - Undated, (5 folders) (Box 287)
  - Undated, (5 folders) (Box 288)
  - Undated, (4 folders) (Box 289)
- National Security Classified Information, circa 1950 (Box CL 1)
  The National Security Classified Information series contains one incomplete report prepared for the Secretary of State for Public Affairs providing an analysis of stereotyped concepts of the United States perpetuated in the Soviet Union and neighboring countries.
  - Russia, United States stereotypes in the Soviet Union, report, circa 1950 (Container 181, same heading) (Box CL 1)
- Oversize, 1920-1990 (Box OV 1-OV 5)
  Material types include posters, photographs, blueprints, notes, newsletters, buttons, a travel satchel, a diploma, a menu, and an award.
  Arranged and described according to the series, containers, and folders from which the items were separated.
  - Personal File
    - Education
      - Barnard Bulletin, 1937, May 7 (Container 5, Education) (Box OV 2)
      - Diploma, Barnard College, 1938 (Container 5, Education) (Box OV 1)
    - Travel satchel, circa 1940s (Box OV 1)
  - Speeches and Writings
    - Books
      - "Cruel and the Kind"; "Divided Heart," outlines, circa 1986 (Container 31, same heading) (Box OV 2)
      - Forever the Wild Mare, promotional materials, Hardy School book fair, posters, 1963 (Container 35, same heading) (Box OV 4)
      - "Meat: The End of the Affair," proposal, notes and outline, circa 1976-1978, undated (Container 36, same heading) (Box OV 2)
  - Subject File
    - "Animal rights and environment buttons," circa 1970-circa 1990 (Box OV 3)
    - Attitudes towards animals, cruelty, "championship steer roping" poster, undated (Container 76, same heading) (Box OV 2)
    - China
      - Shanghai, map, 1945 (Container 94, same heading) (Box OV 5)
      - Zhou, Enlai, signed photograph, 1946 (Container 99, same heading) (Box OV 2)
    - "Declaration of the Rights of Animals," poster, 1990 (Container 100, same heading) (Box OV 2)
    - Egypt; Israel; Palestine, Anti-Terror League flyers, 1947 (Container 103, same heading) (Box OV 2)
    - Euthanasia, blueprints for a euthanasia system, 1972, undated (Container 115, same heading) (Box OV 5)
    - Grandin, Temple, blueprints, 1980 (Container 121, same heading) (Box OV 5)
    - Hornaday, Mary
      - Miscellany, Warren G. Harding presidential campaign poster, 1920 (Container 123, same heading) (Box OV 2)
      - Willis, Raymond E., campaign scrapbook, poster, circa 1938 (Container 124, same heading) (Box OV 2)
    - Montgomery County Humane Society, Md., animal shelter, blueprint and sketch, circa 1974 (Container 151, same heading) (Box OV 5)
    - Rodeos and bullfighting, "boycott the bullfight" poster, undated (Container 172, same heading) (Box OV 5)
    - Schweitzer, Albert, Hôpital Albert Schweitzer, Lambaréné, Gabon; Association International de l'oeuvre du Docteur Albert Schweitzer de Lambaréné, newsletter, 1975 (Container 189, same heading) (Box OV 2)
    - Virginia (film), menu, Café Chambord, New York, N.Y., 1940 (Container 206, same heading) (Box OV 2)
    - Washington Press Club, Washington, D.C., Eleanor Roosevelt Golden Candlestick Award prototype, circa 1964 (Container 211, same heading) (Box OV 6)
  - Photographs
    - China; United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration (UNRRA), "The Bund," Shangai, 1946 (Container 226, same heading) (Box OV 4)
    - Harding, Warren G., New York Herald Tribune dedication, circa 1922 (Box OV 4)